{
    "subject": "resource/Pink_Hope",
    "predicate": "http://www.w3.org/2000/01/rdf-schema#comment",
    "object": "Pink Hope is an Australian non-profit organisation founded by Krystal Barter for educating and preventing about hereditary breast and ovarian cancer.",
    "human_readable": "Pink Hope's comment is Pink Hope is an Australian non-profit organisation founded by Krystal Barter for educating and preventing about hereditary breast and ovarian cancer.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.953721284866333,
            "question": "Is Pink Hope a for-profit or non-profit organization?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8772950768470764,
            "question": "Who founded Pink Hope?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8749378323554993,
            "question": "What does Pink Hope aim to do regarding hereditary breast and ovarian cancer?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8414800763130188,
            "question": "What type of organization is Pink Hope?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.80401611328125,
            "question": "What is Pink Hope?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7452750205993652,
            "question": "Where is Pink Hope based?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6618040204048157,
            "question": "What kind of information does Pink Hope provide?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.644435703754425,
            "question": "What issues does Pink Hope address?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6057420372962952,
            "question": "What are the main areas of focus for Pink Hope?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5394951701164246,
            "question": "What is the primary goal of Pink Hope's work?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Pink Hope's comment is Pink Hope is an Australian non-profit organisation founded by Krystal Barter for educating and preventing about hereditary breast and ovarian cancer.",
            "html": "dbpedia_5068_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are the main areas of focus for Pink Hope?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5068_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What issues does Pink Hope address?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5068_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What kind of information does Pink Hope provide?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5068_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5068_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5068_109.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5068_113.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5068_116.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5068_128.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5068_136.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5068_140.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5068_144.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5068_18.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5068_71.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation of the triple:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents supports the statement that Pink Hope's comment is that it is an Australian non-profit organisation founded by Krystal Barter for educating and preventing about hereditary breast and ovarian cancer.\n\nFrom the documents, we can confirm the following facts:\n\n- Pink Hope is indeed an Australian organisation (file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_5068/re-ranker-msmarco/135.txt)\n- Krystal Barter is the founder of Pink Hope (file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_5068/re-ranker-msmarco/143.txt, file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_5068/re-ranker-msmarco/135.txt)\n- The organisation is focused on educating and preventing about hereditary breast and ovarian cancer (file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_5068/re-ranker-msmarco/115.txt, file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_5068/re-ranker-msmarco/112.txt)\n\nTherefore, the statement \"Pink Hope's comment is Pink Hope is an Australian non-profit organisation founded by Krystal Barter for educating and preventing about hereditary breast and ovarian cancer\" is supported by the information in the documents."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: The provided documents indicate that Pink Hope is indeed an Australian organization focused on education, prevention, and support related to breast and ovarian cancers. Krystal Barter is identified as the founder of Pink Hope, aligning with the statement that it was founded by Krystal Barter for educating and preventing hereditary breast and ovarian cancer."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}